towahbanking.com 2013-05-05

# Towah Privacy Statement

**Towah Members Club Ltd Privacy Statement**

Towah, as Data Controllers are registered with the Information Commissioners Office (ICO) on the Data Protection Public Register. Registration Number: Z2312131

At Towah **["Towah", "we" or "us"]** , we work hard to keep the information you give us safe. We follow strict security procedures on how your personal information is stored and used, to help stop any unauthorised person accessing it.

Please read through this privacy policy carefully, as it is part of our terms of use. By using the my.towah.com and towah.com websites, you are agreeing to be bound by our Terms and Conditions.

This policy describes how we collect, use and look after the information you provide us with when you use Towah’s products and services.

**Using your information**

Collecting this information helps us better understand what you need from us. We use it to offer you products and services that we think will be relevant to you. The main uses of your data are:

• Providing you with the service(s) that you have requested  
• To enable us to review, develop and improve the products and services  
• To send you details of products, services, special offers and rewards that we think will be of interest to you - however, you are able to   
   decide whether or not you want to receive this information  
• To compile statistical analysis of the pages of our website which you visit  
• Link online behaviour to subsequent application / registration details (if these are completed)  
• Evaluate our sites advertising and promotional effectiveness

**Disclosing your information**

Here's when we may provide information about you:

• To employees and agents of Towah to deal with any accounts, products and services provided to you by us or our group companies now   
  or in the future  
• You give us your consent  
• We may use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website   
  and our service and may provide such anonymised aggregate information to third parties for example content partners and advertisers -   
  these statistics will not include information that can be used to identify you  
• The law permits or requires it, or any other regulatory body requests or requires it, even without your consent  
• There is a duty to the public to reveal the information

**Protecting your information**

Any information sent to us by customers via our website is protected by encryption using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. This is industry standard encryption technology that protects your data whilst being sent over the internet from being intercepted and misused by third parties. When it reaches us, we then store it on secure servers so that it can only be read by authorized personnel.

Our website contains links to other websites, which may well have different privacy and security policies to us. Please remember, we don’t have any control over these websites, so we can’t take responsibility for any information you give them.

We take security extremely seriously but as no system is 100% secure, we can’t completely guarantee the protection of your personal information, any more than any other organisation can. So we can’t accept any liability for the loss, theft or misuse of your personal details when they are processed on this website or the internet generally.

**Accessing your information**

You have full access to all information stored about you. You can ask us at any time to give you details about what your information is being used for and who else might see it. You may have to pay a small administration fee for this. Also, please ask if you would like us to change or delete any personal information you have previously given us. If we can we will, but sometimes we have to keep your records for legal reasons. If you'd like us to send your information, you can write to our team at the address at the bottom of this policy.

**Marketing our products and services**

Subject to your consent, we and other Towah companies may contact you by mail, telephone, email, other electronic messaging services (such as text, voice, sound or image messages including using automated calling systems) or fax with information about relevant products and services (including discounts and special offers). We will not disclose your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.

If you wish to receive information and offers from us and other Towah companies, and you have not previously given us your consent, let us know by emailing us at [info@towah.com](mailto:info@towah.com). If you're already receiving information about special offers and rewards from us then don't worry, you don't need to do anything. We'll assume that you're happy to continue receiving information unless we hear from you.

However if you no longer wish to receive such information from us, or other Towah companies, please email us at [info@towah.com](mailto:info@towah.com). Remember that if you say you do not wish to receive any promotional material from us, this will preclude you from receiving any of our special offers or promotions which may be of interest to you.

**Cookies**

By using the Towah website you agree to us storing cookies on your system. Cookies are small files place on your computer’s hard drive, or in your browser memory when you visit our website. They help us speed things up for you when you come back. They tell us what parts of the site you visit, what you like and what's most relevant to you. What cookies don't do is store any personal or confidential information about you.

To ensure you get the best from our websites, we advise that users keep cookies active on their machine whilst visiting our website.

If you'd like to find out more about the cookies we use, what we use them for and how to disable cookies, the Interactive Advertising Bureau has produced a guide (see www.allaboutcookies.org) which explains to users how cookies work and can be managed.

**Transfer of your personal data outside the EU**

Countries outside the European Union may have a lower standard of protection for personal information than that required by the Data Protection Act 1998. If we do this, we will ensure that anyone to whom we transfer your information agrees to treat your information with the same level of protection as provide in the UK.

**Future Changes**

Any changes we make to our policy will be put on my.towah.com and towah.com website. Please check for updates from time to time, so you’re always fully aware of what information is collected, how it’s used and under what circumstances it may be passed on.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information you should write to the Data Protection Officer, Towah, 5th floor, 52-54 Gracechurch Street, London EC3V 0EH

**_This policy was last updated on 11/05/2012_**
